Death comes fast in Texas
The Thicket is a western, crime, thriller film directed by Elliott Lester.
An innocent young man, Jack, goes on an epic quest to rescue his sister Lula after she
has been kidnapped by the violent killer Cut Throat Bill and her gang.
To save her, Jack enlists the help of a crafty bounty hunter named Reginald Jones, a
grave-digging alcoholic son of an ex-slave, and a street-smart prostitute.
The gang tracks Cut Throat Bill into the deadly no-man’s land known as
The Big Thicket — a place where blood and chaos reign.
Reginald Jones, played by Peter Dinklage.
Cut Throat Bill, played by Juliette Lewis.
Jack, played by Levon Hawke.
Jimmie Sue, played by Leslie Grace.
Eustace, played by Gbenga Akinnagbe.
Lula, played by Esmé Creed-Miles.
The Thicket is a 2024 American Western thriller film directed
by Elliott Lester and written by Chris Kelley.
It is a film adaptation of the 2014 novel by Joe R.
It stars Peter Dinklage, Juliette Lewis, Esmé Creed-Miles, Levon Hawke, Andrew
Schulz, James Hetfield, Leslie Grace, and Gbenga Akinnagbe.
The film explores themes of prostitute, bounty hunter,
saloon, based on novel or book, winter.
The tone is dark and intense.